Find your way out.
Valiant One is a war, thriller, action film directed by Steve Barnett.
With tensions between North and South Korea, a US
helicopter crashes on the North side.
The survivors must work together to protect a civilian tech specialist and
find their way out without the help of US military support.
Captain Edward Brockman, played by Chase Stokes.
Specialist Selby, played by Lana Condor.
Josh Weaver, played by Desmin Borges.
Chris Lebold, played by Callan Mulvey.
Binna, played by Diana Tsoy.
Wilson Lee, played by Daniel Jun.
Valiant One is a 2025 American action thriller film directed by
Steve Barnett and co-written by Eric Tipton.
The film was released in the United States on January
31, 2025, by Briarcliff Entertainment.
The tone is intense.